Bloodline is a horror, thriller film directed by Henry Jacobson.
Evan values family above all else, and anyone who gets between him,
his wife, and newborn son learns that the hard way.
But when it comes to violent tendencies, it seems the
apple doesn’t fall far from the tree.
Evan, played by Seann William Scott.
Lauren, played by Mariela Garriga.
Marie, played by Dale Dickey.
Carrie, played by Christie Herring.
Kelly, played by Larsen Thompson.
Overstreet, played by Kevin Carroll.
Bloodline is a 2018 American psychological slasher film directed by Henry
Jacobson and written by Avra Fox-Lerne, Will Honley and Jacobson.
It stars Seann William Scott, Mariela Garriga, Dale Dickey, and Kevin Carroll, and follows Evan Cole
(Scott), a high school guidance counselor who becomes a serial killer, targeting child abusers.
The film is a co-production between Divide/Conquer and Blumhouse Productions.
Bloodline premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 22, 2018, and was released on
September 20, 2019 by Momentum Pictures, receiving mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of murder, serial
killer, slasher, psychological horror.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.